const questions = [

    /* Question 1 */

    {
        numb : 1,
        question: "What is the name of the killer clown in Stephen King's IT?",
        answer:"Pennywise",
        options: [
        'Bozo',
        'Captain Spaulding',
        'Pennywise',
        'Mr. Mime'
        ]
    }, 

    /* Question 2 */

    {
        numb:2,
        question: "What is the name of the main villain in the original 'Texas Chainsaw Massacre'?",
        answer:"Leatherface",
        options: [
            'Leatherface',
            'Pinhead', 
            'Ghostface',
            'Slicey McStabby'
        ]
    }, 

    /* Question 3 */

    {
        numb:3,
        question: "Here's Johnny! What is the name of the hotel where 'The Shining' takes place?",
        answer:"Overlook Hotel",
        options: [
            'The Grand Frontier', 
            'Overwatch Hotel', 
            'Glacier Peak', 
            'Overlook Hotel'
        ]
    }, 

    /* Question 4 */

    {
        numb:4,
        question: "What was the name of the infamous fishing boat used in the climatic shark hunt at the end of 'JAWS'?",
        answer:"Orca",
        options: [
            'Spellbound',
            'Orca',
            'High Tide', 
            'Buoy O Buoy'
        ]
    }, 

    /* Question 5 */

    {
        numb:5,
        question: "How does the (mostly) unseen monster from 'It Follows' decide who to target?",
        answer:"Sexual partners",
        options: [
            'Sexual partners',
            'Virgins', 
            'Atheists', 
            'Females Only', 
        ]
    },

    /* Question 6 */

    {
        numb:6,
        question: "Who was the main protagonist in the 'Scream' series?",
        answer:"Sidney Prescott",
        options: [
            'Dewey Riley', 
            'Sidney Prescott',
            'Casey Becker', 
            'Cotton Weary'
        ]
    },

    /* Question 7 */

    {
        numb:7,
        question: "Before he was caught and burned to death by angry townspeople, Freddy Krueger was a serial killer known as the _________________ ?",
        answer:"Springwood Slasher",
        options: [
            'Elm Street Murderer',
            'Ohio State Stabber', 
            'Springwood Slasher', 
            'Kiddy Killer'
        ]
    },

    /* Question 8 */

    {
        numb:8,
        question: "What is the name of the mysterious hypnotic location that Chris finds himself in during 'Get Out'?",
        answer:"The sunken place",
        options: [
            'The tea cup', 
            'The sunken place',
            'The apple orchard', 
            'The alternate world', 
        ]
    },

    /* Question 9 */

    {
        numb:9,
        question: "The Purge is about a 24-hour period where all crime is legal in America. How often does this happen?",
        answer:"Once a year",
        options: [
            'Once every six months', 
            'Once a month', 
            'Once every five years', 
            'Once a year'
        ]
    },

    /* Question 10 */

    {
        numb:9,
        question: "Michael Myers' mask is actually a mask for what 'Star Trek' character?",
        answer:"James T. Kirk",
        options: [
            'Mr. Spock', 
            'Leonard McCoy', 
            'Jean Luc-Picard', 
            'James T. Kirk', 
        ]
    },


    





]

